<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TextScroll</string>
    <string name="heading">Android</string>
    <string name="subhead">Introduction to Android</string>
    <string name="titlehead">History of Android</string>
    <string name="text">Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software, designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android is developed by a consortium of developers known as the Open Handset Alliance and commercially sponsored by Google. It was unveiled in November 2007, with the first commercial Android device, the HTC Dream, being launched in September 2008. It is free and open-source software.its source code is known as Android Open Source Project (AOSP), which is primarily licensed under the Apache License. However most Android devices ship with additional proprietary software pre-installed,most notably Google Mobile Services (GMS) which includes core apps such as Google Chrome, the digital distribution platform Google Play and associated Google Play Services development platform. About 70 percent of Android smartphones run Google ecosystem.competing Android ecosystems and forks include Fire OS (developed by Amazon) or LineageOS. However the Android name and logo are trademarks of Google which impose standards to restrict uncertified devices outside their ecosystem to use Android branding.
        The source code has been used to develop variants of Android on a range of other electronics, such as game consoles, digital cameras, portable media players, PCs and others, each with a specialized user interface. Some well known derivatives include Android TV for televisions and Wear OS for wearables, both developed by Google. Software packages on Android, which use the APK format, are generally distributed through proprietary application stores like Google Play Store, Samsung Galaxy Store, Huawei AppGallery, Cafe Bazaar, and GetJar, or open source platforms like Aptoide or F-Droid.
        This is a reference from https://www.android.com/ for queries call +919876543210 and mail us on androiddevelopers@gmail.com
</string>
</resources>